<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<xliff xmlns="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.2" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2 xliff-core-1.2-transitional.xsd">
  <file datatype="xml" original="ns-System.Runtime.Remoting.Channels.xml" source-language="en-US" target-language="it-IT">
    <header>
      <tool tool-id="mdxliff" tool-name="mdxliff" tool-version="1.0-efd8310" tool-company="Microsoft" />
      <xliffext:skl_file_name xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">5a83ea4b-dd12-480b-bfc8-267272ef1864a8760d09a78e9a2fbe294d04c88c1e7efe895792.skl</xliffext:skl_file_name>
      <xliffext:version xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">1.2</xliffext:version>
      <xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">a8760d09a78e9a2fbe294d04c88c1e7efe895792</xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash>
      <xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">df6cf590aa3087f6c7c202712eee781c6a3c8f96</xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit>
      <xliffext:ms.lasthandoff xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">05/10/2018</xliffext:ms.lasthandoff>
    </header>
    <body>
      <group id="content" extype="content">
        <trans-unit id="101" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve">
          <source>The <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.Runtime.Remoting.Channels" /&gt;</ph> namespace contains classes that support and handle channels and channel sinks, which are used as the transport medium when a client calls a method on a remote object.</source>
          <target state="translated">Lo spazio dei nomi <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.Runtime.Remoting.Channels" /&gt;</ph> contiene classi che supportano e gestiscono canali e sink di canale, utilizzati come mezzo di trasporto quando un client chiama un metodo su un oggetto remoto.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="102" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Channels are objects that transport messages between applications across remoting boundaries, whether between application domains, processes, or computers.</source>
          <target state="translated">I canali sono oggetti che trasportano messaggi tra le applicazioni attraverso limiti remoti, quali domini di applicazioni, processi o computer.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="103" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>A channel can listen on an endpoint for inbound messages, send outbound messages to another endpoint, or both.</source>
          <target state="translated">Un canale può attendere messaggi in ingresso su un endpoint, inviare messaggi in uscita a un altro endpoint o effettuare entrambe le operazioni.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="104" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>This enables you to plug in a wide range of protocols, even if the common language runtime is not at the other end of the channel.</source>
          <target state="translated">In questo modo è possibile collegarsi a un'ampia gamma di protocolli, anche se Common Language Runtime non è presente all'altra estremità del canale.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="105" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Channels send each object along a chain of channel sink objects prior to sending or after receiving a message.</source>
          <target state="translated">Ogni oggetto lungo una catena di oggetti sink di canale prima dell'invio o dopo la ricezione di un messaggio inviato dai canali.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="106" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>This sink chain contains sinks required for basic channel functionality, such as transport or stack builder sinks, but you can customize the channel sink chain to perform special tasks with a message or a stream.</source>
          <target state="translated">Questa catena di sink contiene sink richiesti per la funzionalità di base del canale, ad esempio sink del generatore di stack o di trasporto, ma è possibile personalizzare la catena di sink di canale per eseguire attività speciali con un messaggio o un flusso.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="107" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Each sink in each chain receives the object, performs a specific operation, and passes it on to the next sink in the chain.</source>
          <target state="translated">Ogni sink in ogni catena riceve l'oggetto esegue un'operazione specifica e lo passa al sink successivo nella catena.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="108" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>There is no rule that the exact object received by a message sink must be passed on to the next sink, though this will often be the case.</source>
          <target state="translated">Non sussiste alcuna regola che l'oggetto esatto ricevuto da un sink di messaggio deve essere passato sink successivo, anche se spesso è il caso.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="109" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>For more information, see <bpt id="p1">[</bpt>Channels<ept id="p1">](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/6e9b60e0-9bc0-47b4-a8ef-3b78585f9a18)</ept> and <bpt id="p2">[</bpt>Sinks and Sink Chains<ept id="p2">](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/516aaab7-5b3d-4c72-83dd-d435c01af8f6)</ept>.</source>
          <target state="translated">Per ulteriori informazioni, vedere <bpt id="p1">[</bpt>canali<ept id="p1">](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/6e9b60e0-9bc0-47b4-a8ef-3b78585f9a18)</ept> e <bpt id="p2">[</bpt>sink e catene di Sink<ept id="p2">](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/516aaab7-5b3d-4c72-83dd-d435c01af8f6)</ept>.</target>       </trans-unit>
      </group>
    </body>
  </file>
</xliff>