<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<xliff xmlns="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.2" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2 xliff-core-1.2-transitional.xsd">
  <file datatype="xml" original="ns-System.Runtime.Remoting.Lifetime.xml" source-language="en-US" target-language="it-IT">
    <header>
      <tool tool-id="mdxliff" tool-name="mdxliff" tool-version="1.0-efd8310" tool-company="Microsoft" />
      <xliffext:skl_file_name xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">5a83ea4b-dd12-480b-bfc8-267272ef18645ac8c7510ea8c5026f390f2936bebfb8b315c4f4.skl</xliffext:skl_file_name>
      <xliffext:version xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">1.2</xliffext:version>
      <xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">5ac8c7510ea8c5026f390f2936bebfb8b315c4f4</xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash>
      <xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">df6cf590aa3087f6c7c202712eee781c6a3c8f96</xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit>
      <xliffext:ms.lasthandoff xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">05/10/2018</xliffext:ms.lasthandoff>
    </header>
    <body>
      <group id="content" extype="content">
        <trans-unit id="101" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve">
          <source>The <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.Runtime.Remoting.Lifetime" /&gt;</ph> namespace contains classes that manage the lifetime of remote objects.</source>
          <target state="translated">Lo spazio dei nomi <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.Runtime.Remoting.Lifetime" /&gt;</ph> contiene classi che gestiscono la durata degli oggetti remoti.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="102" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Traditionally, distributed garbage collection uses reference counts and pinging for control over the lifetime of objects.</source>
          <target state="translated">In genere, la garbage collection distribuita utilizza i conteggi dei riferimenti e il ping per il controllo della durata degli oggetti.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="103" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>This works well when there are a few clients per service, but doesn't scale well when there are thousands of clients per service.</source>
          <target state="translated">Questo funziona bene quando sono presenti alcuni client per ogni servizio, ma non sono adattabili ai casi sono presenti migliaia di client per ogni servizio.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="104" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>The remoting lifetime service associates a lease with each service, and deletes a service when its lease time expires.</source>
          <target state="translated">Il servizio remoto di durata associa un lease di ciascun servizio e consente di eliminare un servizio quando scade la durata del lease.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="105" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>The lifetime service can take on the function of a traditional distributed garbage collector, and it also adjusts well when the numbers of clients per server increases.</source>
          <target state="translated">Il servizio di durata può assumere la funzione di un garbage collector distribuito tradizionali e regola anche anche in caso di aumento del numero di client per ogni server.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="106" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Each application domain contains a lease manager that is responsible for controlling leases in its domain.</source>
          <target state="translated">Ogni dominio dell'applicazione contiene un gestore di lease che è responsabile del controllo dei lease nel dominio.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="107" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>All leases are examined periodically for expired lease times.</source>
          <target state="translated">Tutti i lease vengono esaminati periodicamente per controllarne la scadenza.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="108" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>If a lease has expired, one or more of the lease's sponsors are invoked and given the opportunity to renew the lease.</source>
          <target state="translated">Se un lease è scaduto, uno o più sponsor richiamato e la possibilità di rinnovare il lease.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="109" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>If none of the sponsors decides to renew the lease, the lease manager removes the lease and the object can be collected by the garbage collector.</source>
          <target state="translated">Se nessuno degli sponsor decide di rinnovare il lease, il gestore di lease rimuove il lease e l'oggetto può essere raccolto dal garbage collector.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="110" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>The lease manager maintains a lease list with leases sorted by remaining lease time.</source>
          <target state="translated">Il gestore di lease mantiene un elenco con lease ordinati per tempo rimanente.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="111" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>The leases with the shortest remaining time are stored at the top of the list.</source>
          <target state="translated">I lease con il più breve tempo rimanente vengono archiviati nella parte superiore dell'elenco.</target>       </trans-unit>
      </group>
    </body>
  </file>
</xliff>